[
  {
    "question": "He finish his homework before he went to play football.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He had finished his homework before he went to play football."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "She cook lunch before the children came back.",
    "correctAnswers": ["She had cooked lunch before the children came back."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He travel to Italy before the end of the holiday.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He had travelled to Italy before the end of the holiday."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I leave the amusement park before noon.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had left the amusement park before noon."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "My son go to school before I came home.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My son had gone to school before I came home."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I wash my car before the rain started.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had washed my car before the rain started."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "My daughter said she see this film.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My daughter said she had seen this film."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "The match finish before I turned on the TV.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The match had finished before I turned on the TV."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He remembered that he leave his passport at home.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He remembered that he had left his passport at home."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I thought you invite your sister to the party.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I thought you had invited your sister to the party."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I read his book before he become famous.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I read his book before he had become famous."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He asked me which animals I see in Australia.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He asked me which animals I had seen in Australia."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He said that he pass all the exams.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He said that he had passed all the exams."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I learn German before I visited Berlin.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had learned German before I visited Berlin."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He live in London before he moved to Los Angeles.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He had lived in London before he moved to Los Angeles."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "She clean the house before the guests arrived.",
    "correctAnswers": ["She had cleaned the house before the guests arrived."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I went outside after I hear a strange noise.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I went outside after I had heard a strange noise."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He was sad because he miss the train.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He was sad because he had missed the train."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "We find our dog by the end of the day.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We had found our dog by the end of the day."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I see jaguars in the zoo before I went to Africa.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had seen jaguars in the zoo before I went to Africa."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I meet him before you introduced us.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had met him before you introduced us."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "You said you buy this dress in the shopping mall.",
    "correctAnswers": ["You said you had bought this dress in the shopping mall."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I fall asleep before ten o’clock.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had fallen asleep before ten o’clock."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "They live in Japan for fifteen years before they moved to Spain.",
    "correctAnswers": ["They had lived in Japan for fifteen years before they moved to Spain."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "They have the house for eight years before the fire.",
    "correctAnswers": ["They had had the house for eight years before the fire."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "After they eat breakfast they went to work.",
    "correctAnswers": ["After they had eaten breakfast they went to work."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "They leave the school before the principal came.",
    "correctAnswers": ["They had left the school before the principal came."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "The teacher end the class before we took the notes.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The teacher had ended the class before we took the notes."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "My father give me a phone before I turned fourteen.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My father had given me a phone before I turned fourteen."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I write the paper before two o’clock in the afternoon.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had written the paper before two o’clock in the afternoon."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He finish decorating the house when they came.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He had finished decorating the house when they came."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mum make an apple pie before we returned from camping.",
    "correctAnswers": ["Mum had made an apple pie before we returned from camping."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "The match finish when I reached the stadium.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The match had finished when I reached the stadium."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He read his favourite comic book before going to school.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He had read his favourite comic book before going to school."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "He play hockey in the field before the rain started.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He had played hockey in the field before the rain started."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I helped him to do the task after I finish my work.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I helped him to do the task after I had finished my work."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I was sure that I see her somewhere before.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I was sure that I had seen her somewhere before."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "I go to bed when my parents came back home.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I had gone to bed when my parents came back home."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "We call a taxi when the show was over.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We had called a taxi when the show was over."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"pastPerfect"
  }
]